{
  "results":[
    {
      "question": "What is the Greek name for Piper’s dagger?",
      "correct_answer": "Katoptris",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Sumarbrander", "Anaklusmos", "Helen"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What name did Daedalus use while he was in disguise?",
      "correct_answer": "Quintus",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Mrs. O'leary","Mr. D","Tantalus" ]
      },
    {
      "question" : "What is the full name of Percy Jackson’s little sister?",
      "correct_answer": "Estelle Blofis",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Rachel Elizabeth Dare","Sally Jackson","Silena Beauregard"]
      },
    {
      "question" : "What is the name of Percy’s sword?",
      "correct_answer": "Riptide",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Jack","Perseus","Ivlivs"]
      },
    {
      "question" : "What is the name of Annabeth’s cousin who has his own book series?",
      "correct_answer": "Magnus Chase",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Car Chase","Frank Zhang","Carter Kane"]
      },
    {
      "question" : "What kind of animal can Percy commune with?",
      "correct_answer": "Horses",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Elephants","Dogs","Pigeons"]
      },
    {
      "question" : "In what book did we first meet Nico di Angelo?",
      "correct_answer": "The Titan’s Curse",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Lightning Thief","The House of Hades","The Dark Prophecy"]
      },
    {
      "question" : "What is the name of the hotel that stops you from aging?",
      "correct_answer": "The Lotus Hotel",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Hotel Elixir of Life","Mount Olympus","Hilton Los Angeles"]
      },
    {
      "question" : "What is Apollo’s human name?",
      "correct_answer": "Lester Papadopoulos",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Bob Marley","Aiden Pollock","Peter Johnson"]
      },
    {
    "question" : " What supercharged game do all campers play to prove their battle readiness?",
    "correct_answer": "Capture the Flag",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Climb the Lava Wall","Cannon Balls","Freeze Tag"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Who created the labyrinth?",
    "correct_answer": "Daedalus",
    "incorrect_answers": ["King Midas","Chiron","Achilles"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What is the name of Nico di Angelo’s favorite method of travel?",
    "correct_answer": "Shadow Travel",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Sailing","Iris Travel","Dark-Train"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Bob makes Percy promise to say hello to what?",
    "correct_answer": "The stars",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Kronos","Aphrodite","The fishies"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " How many schools was Percy expelled from over the course of six years?",
    "correct_answer": "Six",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Twelve","Three","Nine"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What is Rachel Dare’s middle name?",
    "correct_answer": "Elizabeth",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Amelia","Sophia","Katelyn"]
    },
    {
    "question" : "How many days did Percy and Annabeth fall into Tartarus?",
    "correct_answer": "Nine",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Twentytwo","Five","Fifteen"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What does Camp Half-Blood look like to mortals?",
    "correct_answer": "A strawberry field",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Summer Camp","Private Mansion","Volcano"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " During the Demigod Civil War, Bunker 9 was used as a command post for which cabin?",
    "correct_answer": "Hephaestus",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Zeus","Athena","Ares"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Where did Percy first meet Rachel Elizabeth Dare?",
    "correct_answer": "The Hoover Dam",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Disney World","Lincoln Memorial","Mount Olympus"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What’s the name of the hellhound Percy befriends?",
    "correct_answer": "Mrs. O'Leary",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Fluffy","Rainbow","Estelle"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What mythical object revived Thalia?",
    "correct_answer": "The Golden Fleece",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Riptide","Bread of Demeter","Caduceus"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Who relieves Annabeth of her burden holding up the sky?",
    "correct_answer": "Artemis",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Luke","Percy","Athna"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What is the name of Luke’s ship?",
    "correct_answer": "The Princess Andromeda",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Argo II","Julia Drusilla","Poseidon"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Who owns C.C's Spa and Resort?",
    "correct_answer": "Circe",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Hestia","Reyna Avila Ramirez-Arellano","Cambodia"]
      },
    {
    "question" : " Who did Polyphemus try to marry?",
    "correct_answer": "Grover",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Annabeth","Piper","Percy"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " The hippocampi are a combination of what two animals?",
    "correct_answer": "Horse and Fish",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Hippo and Horse","Fish and Bird","Bird and Hippo"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What is the name of the ability that Piper uses to get people to do what she wants?",
    "correct_answer": "Charmspeak",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Shouting","Hypnosis","Politely asking"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What does Tristan McLean do for a living?",
    "correct_answer": "Actor",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Bodybuilder","Clerk","Fisherman"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Who currently leads the Hunters of Artemis?",
    "correct_answer": "Thaila Grace",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Annabeth Chase","Grover","Zoë Nightshade"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What subject does Mr. Brunner teach?",
    "correct_answer": "Latin",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Algebra I","English","Art"]
      },
    {
    "question" : " Who is the earthshaker, the stormbringer, the father of horses?",
    "correct_answer": "Poseidon",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Zeus","Hades","Apollo"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What two creatures attack Percy at the top of the Gateway Arch?",
    "correct_answer": "Echidna and the Chimera",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Kampê and a Cyclops","Minotaur and Gorgon","Scylla and Charybdis"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Where do ordinary souls go after they’ve died in Greek Mythology?",
    "correct_answer": "The Fields of Asphodel",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Elysium","Hel","Duat"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Swearing on what river is the most serious oath you can make?",
    "correct_answer": "The River Styx",
    "incorrect_answers": ["The River Lethe","The Hudson River","The River Phlegethon"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " The River Lethe is also known as the river of what?",
    "correct_answer": "Forgetfulness",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Night","Hatred","Fire"]
    },
    {
    "question" : "After calling Hera 'Her Majesty, the Loose Canon,' what does the goddess threaten to turn Thalia into?",
    "correct_answer": "An aardvark",
    "incorrect_answers": ["A peacock","A cow","A hippopotamus"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What is the name of the school Percy attends in the first book?",
    "correct_answer": "Yancy Academy",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Wilderness School","Goode High School","Westover Hall"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Where is the Lotus Hotel located?",
    "correct_answer": "Las Vegas",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Los Angeles","Topeka","Brooklynn"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Don from Camp Jupiter is what kind of creature?",
    "correct_answer": "A Faun",
    "incorrect_answers": ["A Donut","An Elephant","A Nymph"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Who does Grover have an Empathy Link with?",
    "correct_answer": "Percy",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Annabeth","Don","Coach Hedge"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Which cabin at Camp Half-Blood has the least amount of inhabitants?",
    "correct_answer": "Hera",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Zeus","Poseidon","Hades"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Before renovation, the children of minor gods stayed in which cabin?",
    "correct_answer": "Hermes (Cabin 11)",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Unwanteds (Cabin 0)","Zues (Cabin 1)","Hera (Cabin 2)"]
    },
    {
    "question" : "Which goddess controls The Mist?",
    "correct_answer": "Hecate",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Hera","Hestia","Hebe"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What does Meg McCaffrey’s outfit remind Apollo of?",
    "correct_answer": "A traffic light",
    "incorrect_answers": ["An icecream cone","Abstract art","A crime scene"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Who is the current architect of Olympus?",
    "correct_answer": "Annabeth",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Athena","Daedalus","Apollo"]
    },
    {
    "question" : "Why did Luke’s mother go insane?",
    "correct_answer": "She tried to become the Oracle of Delphi",
    "incorrect_answers": ["She angered Dionysus","She tripped and cracked her head open","She was tortured by Iapetus"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " Who is Charybdis’ sister?",
    "correct_answer": "Scylla",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Medusa","Arachne","Hydra"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What animal did Circe turn Percy into?",
    "correct_answer": "Guinea pig",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Horse","Squirrel","Cow"]
    },
    {
    "question" : " What is Thalia afraid of?",
    "correct_answer": "Heights",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Spiders","Small spaces","Trees"]
    },
    {
    "question" : "What plant does Triptolemus turn Nico into?",
    "correct_answer": "Corn",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Pine Tree","Sunflower","Watermelon"]
    }
  ]
}
